http://www.mmwebserv.com/privacy-statement

Privacy statement
Your privacy on micromedic.com or mmwebserv.comThis website is administered by Micro Medic, Inc. The primary purpose of micromedic.com and mmwebserv.com is to be a dynamic resource and business tool. We want you to feel secure when visiting our site and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so. The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit.What information do we gather?Information on micromedic.com and mmwebserv.com is gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our site's technology); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information). One example of information we collect indirectly is through our Internet access logs. When you access micromedic.com, your Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs. We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which we describe in this Privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to our sites - for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you. The cookies we use identify you merely as a number. (If you are uncomfortable regarding cookies use, please keep in mind you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser.) We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. On our site, we collect information when you contact us to ask questions or begin a business relationship. This information is not available to us unless you knowingly send it to us by clicking a button to send it. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.How do we use this information?We analyze it to determine what is most effective about our site, to help us identify ways to improve it, and eventually, to determine how we can tailor our sites to make them more effective. We may also use data for other purposes, which we would describe to you at the point we collect the information.Will we share this with outside parties?We will not sell individual information and will share it only internally or with our advisers. But again, it is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.What about sensitive personal data?We do not generally seek to collect sensitive personal data through this site. If we do seek to collect such data, we will ask you to consent to our proposed uses of the data. We may also collect some sensitive personal data incidentally. By providing us with unsolicited sensitive personal data, you consent to our using the data subject to applicable law as described in this Privacy Statement. The references to "sensitive personal data" are to the various categories of personal data identified by European and other data privacy laws as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories comprise personal identity numbers, personal data about personality and private life, racial or ethnic origin, nationality, political opinions, membership of political parties or movements, religious, philosophical or other similar beliefs, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, genetic code, addictions, sexual life, property matters or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities).Do we give you access to your information?You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you and, if we do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by contacting us via our webmaster at mail:micromedic.com:webmaster.What about data security?We take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your data on micromedic.com. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. We are interested in maintaining your privacy and creating a valuable resource for you to use. If you have any questions now or during your visit, please contact us via our webmaster at mail:micromedic.com:webmaster.
Micro Medic
